Guide to NYU Publications: Preservation Copies 1832-1994 RG 1.0
New York University Archives
New York University Publications (preservation copies)
1832-1999
RG 1.0
New York University Archives
216.0 linear feet
This collection contains preservation copies of various New York University publications, primarily yearbooks, dating from the 1990s back to the first years of the University's history.
New York University.
Arrangement
The files are grouped into 1 series.
Publications
Scope and Content Note
The collection is comprised of preservation copies of yearbooks and other New York University publications that are stored off site.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions. This collection is in
off-site storage
.
History of New York University Publications
Publications and yearbooks that make up the collection include: The Violet, The Commerce Violet, The Album, The Torch, New York University Bulletin, University Bibliography, and commencement programs.
New York University. Students. Periodicals.; College students |z New York (State) |z New York |v Periodicals.; Commencement ceremonies |z New York (State) |z New York |v Periodicals.; Periodicals.; School yearbooks.; Student newspapers and periodicals |z New York (State) |z New York.
- Series I
  - Commerce, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Commerce, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Item 2)
    General note
    bar code: 3 1142 040584818
  - Commerce, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Commerce, 1928 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Commerce, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Commerce, 1934-1940 (Box 2, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584826
  - Commerce, 1943-1946 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Commerce, 1947-1956 (Box 3, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584834
  - Album, 1933-1947 (Box 4, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584842
  - Album, 1948-1963 (Box 5, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584859
  - Violet, 1963-1972 (Box 6, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584867
  - Violet, 1946-1962 (Box 7, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584883
  - Torch, 1989-1993 (Box 8, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584875
  - BPA/Stern, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - BPA/Stern, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - BPA/Stern, 1987 (Box 8, Item 4)
  - BPA/Stern, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Item 5)
  - Commerce, 1912 (Box 9, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584891
  - Commerce, 1916 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - Commerce, 1920-1923 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - Commerce, 1926-1927 (Box 9, Item 4)
  - Commerce, 1929-1933 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - Commerce, 1958-1969 (Box 10, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584909
  - Education, 1952-1966 (Box 11, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584917
  - Education, 1931-1935 (Box 12, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584925
  - Education, 1934-1941 (Box 12, Item 2)
  - Education, 1943-1948 (Box 12, Item 3)
  - Education, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Item 4)
  - Album, 1924-1932 (Box 13, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584933
  - Album, 1964-1969 (Box 14, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584941
  - WSUC, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Item 2)
  - Torch, 1977-1983 (Box 14, Item 3)
  - Torch, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Item 4)
  - Torch, 1988 (Box 14, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1896 (Box 15, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584958
  - Violet, 1899 (Box 15, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1903 (Box 15, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1905 (Box 15, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1906 (Box 15, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1907 (Box 15, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1909 (Box 16, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584966
  - Violet, 1914 (Box 16, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1915 (Box 16, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1917 (Box 16, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1936 (Box 16, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1938 (Box 16, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1940 (Box 16, Item 7)
  - Violet, 1953 (Box 16, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1959 (Box 16, Item 9)
  - Education, 1954 (Box 17, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584974
  - Education, 1956 (Box 17, Item 2)
  - Education, 1958 (Box 17, Item 3)
  - Education, 1959 (Box 17, Item 4)
  - Education, 1960 (Box 17, Item 5)
  - Education, 1961 (Box 17, Item 6)
  - Summer School Album, 1935 (Box 17, Item 7)
  - Education, 1962 (Box 18, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584982
  - Education, 1963 (Box 18, Item 2)
  - Education, 1965 (Box 18, Item 3)
  - Education, 1969 (Box 18, Item 4)
  - Education, 1972 (Box 18, Item 5)
  - Education, 1973 (Box 18, Item 6)
  - Commerce, 1950 (Box 19, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040584990
  - Commerce, 1953 (Box 19, Item 2)
  - Commerce, 1962 (Box 19, Item 3)
  - Commerce, 1964 (Box 19, Item 4)
  - Commerce, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Item 5)
  - Commerce, 1950 (Box 20, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585005
  - Album, 1928 (Box 21, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585013
  - Album, 1930 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Album, 1931 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - Album, 1936 (Box 21, Item 4)
  - Album, 1953 (Box 21, Item 5)
  - Album, 1958 (Box 21, Item 6)
  - Album, 1967 (Box 21, Item 7)
  - Album, 1928 (Box 21, Item 8)
  - Album, 1930 (Box 21, Item 9)
  - Album, 1931 (Box 21, Item 10)
  - Album, 1936 (Box 21, Item 11)
  - Album, 1953 (Box 21, Item 12)
  - Album, 1958 (Box 21, Item 13)
  - Album, 1967 (Box 21, Item 14)
  - Violet, 1937 (Box 22, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585021
  - Album, 1930 (Box 22, Item 2)
  - Album, 1931 (Box 22, Item 3)
  - Album, 1966 (Box 22, Item 4)
  - Album, 1967 (Box 22, Item 5)
  - Torch, 1977 (Box 22, Item 6)
  - Torch, 1982 (Box 22, Item 7)
  - Torch, 1989 (Box 22, Item 8)
  - Commerce, 1967 (Box 22, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1892 (Box 23, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585039
  - Violet, 1897 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1899 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1901 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1902 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1903 (Box 23, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1906 (Box 23, Item 7)
  - Violet, 1909 (Box 23, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1910 (Box 23, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1914 (Box 24, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585047
  - Violet, 1915 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1916 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1917 (Box 24, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1918 (Box 24, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1919 (Box 24, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1920 (Box 24, Item 7)
  - Violet, 1921 (Box 24, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1924 (Box 24, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1925 (Box 25, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585054
  - Violet, 1926 (Box 25, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1927 (Box 25, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1928 (Box 25, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1929 (Box 25, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1930 (Box 25, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1932 (Box 25, Item 7)
  - Violet, 1933 (Box 25, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1934 (Box 25, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1932 (Box 26, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585062
  - Violet, 1935 (Box 26, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1936 (Box 26, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1937 (Box 26, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1939 (Box 26, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1940 (Box 26, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1941 (Box 26, Item 7)
  - Violet, 1942 (Box 26, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1943 (Box 26, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1944 (Box 26, Item 10)
  - Violet, 1947 (Box 26, Item 11)
  - Violet, 1951 (Box 26, Item 12)
  - Violet, 1952 (Box 26, Item 13)
  - Violet, 1946 (Box 26, Item 14)
  - Violet, 1953 (Box 27, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585070
  - Violet, 1954 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Violet, 1955 (Box 27, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1956 (Box 27, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1957 (Box 27, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1958 (Box 27, Item 6)
  - Violet, 1959 (Box 27, Item 7)
  - Violet, 1960 (Box 27, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1962 (Box 27, Item 9)
  - Violet, 1963 (Box 27, Item 10)
  - Violet, 1964 (Box 27, Item 11)
  - Violet, 1967 (Box 28, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585088
  - NYU Alumnus, 1921-1922 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1922-1923 (Box 28, Item 3)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Item 4)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1924-1925 (Box 28, Item 5)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1925-1926 (Box 28, Item 6)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1926-1927 (Box 28, Item 7)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1927-1928 (Box 28, Item 8)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1928-1929 (Box 28, Item 9)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1929-1930 (Box 29, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585096
  - NYU Alumnus, 1930-1931 (Box 29, Item 2)
  - NYU Alumnus, 1931-1932 (Box 29, Item 3)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Alumni Directory, 1976 (Box 29, Item 4)
  - Builders of Enterprise, 1950 (Box 29, Item 5)
  - Proceedings of the Golden Anniversary of the School of Commercial Science, School of Commerce, Accounts and Finance, 1950 (Box 29, Item 6)
  - Arts and Science, Spring, 1962-1967 (Box 29, Item 7)
  - Gnereal Alumni Catalgo, 1916 (Box 29, Item 8)
  - College of Applied Science Alumni Catalog, 1833-1905 (Box 29, Item 9)
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1887-1988 (Box 30, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585104
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1888-1989 (Box 30, Item 2)
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1889-1990 (Box 30, Item 3)
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1890-1991 (Box 30, Item 4)
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1891-1992 (Box 30, Item 5)
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1892-1993 (Box 30, Item 6)
  - University of the City of New York Bulletins, 1893-1994 (Box 30, Item 7)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1894-1995 (Box 30, Item 8)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1895-1996 (Box 30, Item 9)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1896-1997 (Box 30, Item 10)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1897-1998 (Box 30, Item 11)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1898-1999 (Box 30, Item 12)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1899-1990 (Box 30, Item 13)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1901-1902 (Box 30, Item 14)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1902-1903 (Box 30, Item 15)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1903-1904 (Box 31, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585112
  - NYU Bulletins, 1904-1905 (Box 31, Item 2)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1905-1906 (Box 31, Item 3)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1906-1907 (Box 31, Item 4)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1907-1908 (Box 31, Item 5)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1909-1910 (Box 31, Item 6)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1910-1911 (Box 31, Item 7)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1911-1912 (Box 32, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585120
  - NYU Bulletins, 1912-1913 (Box 32, Item 2)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1913-1914 (Box 32, Item 3)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1915-1916 (Box 32, Item 4)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1916-1917 (Box 32, Item 5)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1918-1919 (Box 32, Item 6)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1916-1917 (Box 32, Item 7)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1917-1918 (Box 32, Item 8)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1919-1920 (Box 33, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585138
  - NYU Bulletins, 1920-1921 (Box 33, Item 2)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1921-1922 (Box 33, Item 3)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1922-1923 (Box 33, Item 4)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1923-1924 (Box 33, Item 5)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Item 6)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1925-1926 (Box 33, Item 7)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1927-1928 (Box 33, Item 8)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1931-1933 (Box 33, Item 9)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1935-1936 (Box 34, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585146
  - NYU Bulletins, 1936-1937 (Box 34, Item 2)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1937-1938 (Box 34, Item 3)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1938-1939 (Box 34, Item 4)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Item 5)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Item 6)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Item 7)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1942-1943 (Box 34, Item 8)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1944-1945 (Box 34, Item 9)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1945-1946 (Box 34, Item 10)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1946-1947 (Box 34, Item 11)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1947-1948 (Box 34, Item 12)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Item 13)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Item 14)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1950-1951 (Box 34, Item 15)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Item 16)
  - NYU Bulletins, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Item 17)
  - The Hall of American Artists, undated (Box 34, Item 18)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, undated (Box 34, Item 19)
  - University Bibliography, 1931 (Box 35, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585153
  - University Bibliography, 1933-1934 (Box 35, Item 2)
  - University Bibliography, 1935 (Box 35, Item 3)
  - University Bibliography, 1936 (Box 35, Item 4)
  - University Bibliography, 1937 (Box 35, Item 5)
  - University Bibliography, 1938 (Box 35, Item 6)
  - University Bibliography, 1939 (Box 35, Item 7)
  - University Bibliography, 1940 (Box 35, Item 8)
  - University Bibliography, 1941 (Box 35, Item 9)
  - University Bibliography, 1942 (Box 35, Item 10)
  - University Bibliography, 1943 (Box 35, Item 11)
  - University Bibliography, 1944 (Box 35, Item 12)
  - University Bibliography, 1945 (Box 35, Item 13)
  - University Bibliography, 1942-19194248-1948 (Box 35, Item 14)
  - University Bibliography, 1947 (Box 35, Item 15)
  - University Bibliography, 1948 (Box 35, Item 16)
  - University Bibliography, 1949-1952 (Box 35, Item 17)
  - University Bibliography, 1949 (Box 35, Item 18)
  - University Bibliography, 1950 (Box 35, Item 19)
  - University Bibliography, 1953-1955 (Box 35, Item 20)
  - William Lyndon Wright, a Memoir, undated (Box 35, Item 21)
  - William Henry Nichols, undated (Box 35, Item 22)
  - Cornelius Baker, undated (Box 35, Item 23)
  - A Tribute to Elmer Ellsworth Brown, undated (Box 35, Item 24)
  - Henry Mitchel MacCracken In Memoriam, undated (Box 35, Item 25)
  - Biographical History of NYU V.2, undated (Box 36, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585161
  - NYU, 1832-1932 (Box 36, Item 2)
  - Graduate School of Arts & Science of NYU: A History, undated (Box 36, Item 3)
  - The Urban University Coming of Age, 1971 (Box 36, Item 4)
  - Detication of the Elmer Ellsworth Brown House, undated (Box 36, Item 5)
  - NYU Commencements, 1901-1902 (Box 36, Item 6)
  - NYU Commencements, 1910-1911 (Box 36, Item 7)
  - NYU Commencements, 1914 (Box 36, Item 8)
  - NYU Commencements, 1917 (Box 36, Item 9)
  - NYU Commencements, 1918 (Box 37, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585179
  - NYU Commencements, 1919 (Box 37, Item 2)
  - NYU Commencements, 1918-1919 (Box 37, Item 3)
  - NYU Commencements, 1921 (Box 37, Item 4)
  - NYU Commencements, 1926 (Box 37, Item 5)
  - NYU Commencements, 1927 (Box 37, Item 6)
  - NYU Commencements, 1929 (Box 37, Item 7)
  - NYU Commencements, 1932 (Box 37, Item 8)
  - NYU Commencements, 1933 (Box 37, Item 9)
  - NYU Commencements, 1934 (Box 37, Item 10)
  - NYU Commencements, 1935 (Box 37, Item 11)
  - NYU Commencements, 1936 (Box 37, Item 12)
  - NYU Commencements, 1937 (Box 37, Item 13)
  - NYU Commencements, 1938 (Box 37, Item 14)
  - NYU Commencements, 1939 (Box 37, Item 15)
  - NYU Commencements, 1940 (Box 37, Item 16)
  - NYU Commencements, 1941 (Box 37, Item 17)
  - NYU Commencements, 1942 (Box 37, Item 18)
  - NYU Commencements, 1943 (Box 37, Item 19)
  - NYU Commencements, 1944 (Box 37, Item 20)
  - NYU Commencements, 1945-1953 (Box 37, Item 21)
  - NYU Commencements, 1954-1961 (Box 37, Item 22)
  - Commerce Violet, 1952 (Box 38, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585187
  - NYU Commencements, 1962-1967 (Box 38, Item 2)
  - NYU Commencements, 1975 (Box 38, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1933-1945 (Box 39, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585195
  - Violet, 1904-1919 (Box 40, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040585203
  - Violet, 1920-1932 (Box 41, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593611
  - Album, 1928-1936 (Box 42, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593629
  - Album, 1938 (Box 42, Item 2)
  - Album, 1939-1941 (Box 43, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593637
  - Album, 1943-1956 (Box 43, Item 2)
  - Album, 1958-1974 (Box 44, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593645
  - Torch, 1975-1978 (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Torch, 1981 (Box 45, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593652
  - Torch, 1981 (Box 46, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593660
  - Torch, 1982 (Box 46, Item 2)
  - Torch, 1982 (Box 47, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593678
  - Torch, 1983 (Box 48, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593686
  - Torch, 1983 (Box 49, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593702
  - Torch, 1983 (Box 50, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593710
  - Torch, 1985 (Box 50, Item 2)
  - Torch, 1985 (Box 51, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593728
  - Torch, 1985 (Box 52, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593751
  - Torch, 1986 (Box 53, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593736
  - Torch, 1986 (Box 54, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593744
  - Torch, 1987 (Box 55, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593769
  - Torch, 1988 (Box 55, Item 2)
  - Torch, 1989 (Box 55, Item 3)
  - Torch, 1989 (Box 56, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593694
  - Torch, 1990 (Box 57, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040593777
  - Torch, 1991 (Box 57, Item 2)
  - Torch, 1993 (Box 57, Item 3)
  - Freshman Regular, 1990 (Box 57, Item 4)
  - Freshman Regular, 1994 (Box 57, Item 5)
  - The Album (5 copies), 1985 (Box 58, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581467
  - The Album, 1986 (Box 58, Item 2)
  - The Album, 1988 (Box 58, Item 3)
  - The Album, 1989 (Box 58, Item 4)
  - The Album, 1990 (Box 58, Item 5)
  - The Album, 1991 (Box 58, Item 6)
  - The Album, 1995 (Box 58, Item 7)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1925 (Box 58, Item 8)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1930 (Box 58, Item 9)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1931 (Box 58, Item 10)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1932 (Box 58, Item 11)
  - Violet (5 copies), 1936 (Box 59, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581475
  - Violet (4 copies), 1937 (Box 59, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1938 (Box 59, Item 3)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1903 (Box 60, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581483
  - Violet (4 copies), 1904 (Box 60, Item 2)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1905 (Box 60, Item 3)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1897 (Box 61, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581509
  - Violet, 1898 (Box 61, Item 2)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1899 (Box 61, Item 3)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1900 (Box 61, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1901 (Box 61, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1901 (Box 61, Item 6)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1981 (Box 62, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581517
  - Violet (2 copies), 1892 (Box 62, Item 2)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1893 (Box 62, Item 3)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1894 (Box 62, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1895 (Box 62, Item 5)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1896 (Box 62, Item 6)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1933 (Box 63, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581525
  - Violet (4 copies), 1934 (Box 63, Item 2)
  - Violet (5 copies), 1935 (Box 63, Item 3)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1944 (Box 64, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581533
  - Violet, 1945 (Box 64, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1946 (Box 64, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1946 (Box 64, Item 4)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1947 (Box 64, Item 5)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1948 (Box 64, Item 6)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1949 (Box 64, Item 7)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1950 (Box 64, Item 8)
  - Violet, 1910 (Box 65, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581541
  - Violet (2 copies), 1911 (Box 65, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1912 (Box 65, Item 3)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1913 (Box 65, Item 4)
  - Violet (5 copies), 1914 (Box 65, Item 5)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1915 (Box 65, Item 6)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1906 (Box 66, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581558
  - Violet (3 copies), 1907 (Box 66, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1908 (Box 66, Item 3)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1909 (Box 66, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1950 (Box 67, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581566
  - Violet, 1951 (Box 67, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1952 (Box 67, Item 3)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1953 (Box 67, Item 4)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1954 (Box 67, Item 5)
  - Violet, 1955 (Box 67, Item 6)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1956 (Box 67, Item 7)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1957 (Box 67, Item 8)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1927 (Box 68, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581574
  - Violet (2 copies), 1928 (Box 68, Item 2)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1930 (Box 68, Item 3)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1922 (Box 69, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581582
  - Violet (3 copies), 1923 (Box 69, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1924 (Box 69, Item 3)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1925 (Box 69, Item 4)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1926 (Box 69, Item 5)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1916 (Box 70, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581590
  - Violet (5 copies), 1917 (Box 70, Item 2)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1918 (Box 70, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1919 (Box 70, Item 4)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1920 (Box 70, Item 5)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1930 (Box 71, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 040581608
  - Violet (3 copies), 1931 (Box 71, Item 2)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1932 (Box 71, Item 3)
  - Senior Violet (4 copies), 1932 (Box 71, Item 4)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1938 (Box 72, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254154
  - Violet (3 copies), 1939 (Box 72, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1940 (Box 72, Item 3)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1941 (Box 72, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1942 (Box 72, Item 5)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1943 (Box 72, Item 6)
  - The Album, 1926 (Box 73, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254162
  - The Album (4 copies), 1927 (Box 73, Item 2)
  - The Album- Senior Album (4 copies), 1927 (Box 73, Item 3)
  - Violet (4 copies), 1965 (Box 74, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254188
  - Violet (2 copies), 1966 (Box 74, Item 2)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1967 (Box 74, Item 3)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1969 (Box 74, Item 4)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1928 (Box 75, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254196
  - The Album (2 copies), 1929 (Box 75, Item 2)
  - The Album, 1930 (Box 75, Item 3)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1970 (Box 76, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254204
  - Violet red (3 copies), 1970 (Box 76, Item 2)
  - Violet (3 copies), 1971 (Box 76, Item 3)
  - Violet, 1972 (Box 76, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1973 (Box 76, Item 5)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1926 (Box 76, Item 6)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1930 (Box 77, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254212
  - The Album (4 copies), 1931 (Box 77, Item 2)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1932 (Box 77, Item 3)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1933 (Box 78, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254220
  - The Album (3 copies), 1934 (Box 78, Item 2)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1935 (Box 78, Item 3)
  - The Album, 1936 (Box 78, Item 4)
  - The Album, 1937 (Box 78, Item 5)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1943 (Box 79, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254170
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1949 (Box 79, Item 2)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet (2 copies), 1967 (Box 79, Item 3)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet, 1969 (Box 79, Item 4)
  - Bellevue Medical Violet (2 copies), 1975 (Box 79, Item 5)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1932 (Box 79, Item 6)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1934 (Box 79, Item 7)
  - Education Violet, 1940 (Box 79, Item 8)
  - Education Violet, 1943 (Box 79, Item 9)
  - Education Violet, 1944 (Box 79, Item 10)
  - Education Violet, 1946 (Box 79, Item 11)
  - Education Violet, 1948 (Box 79, Item 12)
  - Education Violet, 1951 (Box 79, Item 13)
  - The Album, 1938 (Box 80, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254238
  - The Album (2 copies), 1939 (Box 80, Item 2)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1940 (Box 80, Item 3)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1941 (Box 80, Item 4)
  - The Album, 1944 (Box 80, Item 5)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1946 (Box 80, Item 6)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1947 (Box 80, Item 7)
  - The Album, 1948 (Box 80, Item 8)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1949 (Box 80, Item 9)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1958 (Box 81, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254246
  - Violet (2 copies), 1959 (Box 81, Item 2)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1960 (Box 81, Item 3)
  - Violet (6 copies), 1961 (Box 81, Item 4)
  - Violet, 1962 (Box 81, Item 5)
  - Violet (2 copies), 1964 (Box 81, Item 6)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1950 (Box 82, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254253
  - The Album (4 copies), 1952 (Box 82, Item 2)
  - The Album (4 copies), 1953 (Box 82, Item 3)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1954 (Box 82, Item 4)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1955 (Box 83, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254261
  - The Album (2 copies), 1956 (Box 83, Item 2)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1957 (Box 83, Item 3)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1958 (Box 83, Item 4)
  - The Album, 1959 (Box 83, Item 5)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1960 (Box 83, Item 6)
  - The Album (3 copies), 1961 (Box 83, Item 7)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1962 (Box 84, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254279
  - The Album, 1965 (Box 84, Item 2)
  - The Album (4 copies), 1966 (Box 84, Item 3)
  - The Album (4 copies), 1967 (Box 84, Item 4)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1968 (Box 84, Item 5)
  - The Album, 1975 (Box 84, Item 6)
  - The Album (2 copies), 1977 (Box 84, Item 7)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1952 (Box 85, Item 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254287
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1953 (Box 85, Item 2)
  - Education Violet (3 copies), 1954 (Box 85, Item 3)
  - Education Violet (2 copies), 1955 (Box 85, Item 4)